University Senate; Records ua200
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Formal Reports and Publications, 1946 - 1999; 5; 0.67 cubic ft.
  - Annual Report of the Faculty Council, 1963-1964 (Box 1 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 14)
  - Annual Report of the Faculty Council, 1965-1966 (Box 1 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 15)
  - Annual Reports of the Faculty Senate and Senate Councils, 1966-1967; 1969-1970 (Box 1 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 16)
  - Annual Report, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 17)
  - Annual Report, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 18)
  - Annual Report, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 19)
  - Annual Report, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 20)
  - Annual Report, 1974-1975 (Box 1 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 21)
  - Annual Report, 1975-1976 (Box 1 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 22)
  - Mission Statement of the University Department Responses (Folder 1 of 2), 1976 (Box 1 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 23)
  - Mission Statement of the University Department Responses (Folder 2 of 2), 1976 (Box 1 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 24)
  - Annual Report, 1976-1977 (Box 2 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 1)
  - Mission Statement of the University, 1976-1977 (Box 2 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 2)
  - Annual Report, 1977-1978 (Box 2 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 3)
  - Annual Report, 1978-1979 (Box 2 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 4)
  - Annual Report, 1979-1980; 1981-1982 (Box 2 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 5)
  - Annual Report, 1982-1983; 1985-1986 (Box 2 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 6)
  - Annual Report, 1987-1988; 1988-1989 (Box 2 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 7)
  - University Senate Newsletter, 1989 (Box 2 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 8)
  - Annual Report, 1989-1990 (Box 2 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 9)
  - Your Senate, 1991-1992 (Box 2 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 10)
  - Annual Report, 1991-1992; 1994-1995 (Box 2 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 11)
  - Annual Report, 1995-1996 (Box 2 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 12)
  - Annual Report, 1996-1997 (Box 2 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 13)
  - Annual Report, 1997-1998 (Box 2 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 14)
  - Annual Report, 1998-1999 (Box 2 (5-Formal Reports and Publications), Folder 15)
  - Report of the UALBANY Task Force on Undergraduate Writing Instruction- Revised Draft, 2006-2007
  - University Faculty Senate Report, 2008-01-31-2008-02-02
  - Memo RE: Deactivation of Academic Programs, 2010-10-01
  - General Education Task Force Report, 2010-12-02
  - Email RE: Report to Senate Statistic Clarification, 2011-04-18
  - Honor's College Fifth Year Report, 2012-06-15
  - Report on Academic Profile of UAlbany Student-Athletes, 2012
- Bylaws, Charters, and Faculty Handbooks, 1948-20156; 6; 0.33 cubic ft.
  - Faculty Handbook, 1948; 1952; 1962-1963; 1966 (Box 1 (6-Bylaws, Charters, and Faculty Handbooks), Folder 1)
  - Faculty Handbook, 1966-1967; 1971-1972 (Box 1 (6-Bylaws, Charters, and Faculty Handbooks), Folder 2)
  - Faculty Handbook, 1972-1974 (Box 1 (6-Bylaws, Charters, and Faculty Handbooks), Folder 3)
  - Faculty Handbook, 1975-1978 (Box 1 (6-Bylaws, Charters, and Faculty Handbooks), Folder 4)
  - Faculty Handbook, 1979-1982 (Box 1 (6-Bylaws, Charters, and Faculty Handbooks), Folder 5)
  - Faculty Handbook, 1984-1985; 1986-1987 (Box 1 (6-Bylaws, Charters, and Faculty Handbooks), Folder 6)
  - Faculty Handbook, 1989-1990; 1990-1992; 1992 (Box 1 (6-Bylaws, Charters, and Faculty Handbooks), Folder 7)
  - University Faculty Senate Bylaws, 2009-2010
  - University Faculty Senate Governance Handbook, 2011-2012
  - Senate Charter (with updates), 2003-2004
  - Charter of the University Senate (with revisions), 2010
  - Charter of the University Senate, 2012
  - Charter of the University Senate, 2008
  - Combined Index to the Faculty Bylaws of the University at Albany and the Charter of the University Senate, 2007
  - Combined Index to the Faculty Bylaws of the University at Albany and the Charter of the University Senate with Fessler comments, 2011
- Membership Lists, 1966-1998; 7; 0.33 cubic ft.
  Lists of members of the University Senate, including the membership of the specific councils and committees and student memberships.
  - Membership Lists of the Faculty Senate, 1966-1967; 1969-1970 (Box 1 (7-Membership Lists), Folder 1)
  - Membership Lists, 1970-1971; 1974/1975 (Box 1 (7-Membership Lists), Folder 2)
  - Membership Lists, 1975-1976; 1980-1981 (Box 1 (7-Membership Lists), Folder 3)
  - Membership Lists, 1981-1982; 1986-1987 (Box 1 (7-Membership Lists), Folder 4)
  - Membership Lists, 1987-1988; 1990-1991 (Box 1 (7-Membership Lists), Folder 5)
  - Membership Lists, 1991-1992; 1993-1994 (Box 1 (7-Membership Lists), Folder 6)
  - Membership Lists, 1994-1995; 1996-1997 (Box 1 (7-Membership Lists), Folder 7)
  - Membership Lists, 1997-1998 (Box 1 (7-Membership Lists), Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1966-1999; 8; 1 cubic ft.
  This series consists of the correspondence of the Chair of the University Senate, including Ronald A. Bosco (1983-84, 1989-90), William F. Hammond (1987-88, 1988-89), William Lanford (1990-91), Audrey Champagne (1993-94), Carlos Santiago (1996-97), and Sue Faerman (1997-98). It includes correspondence with the President of the University, the Chairs of the Councils of the University Senate, the University Faculty Senate, and the State of New York.
  - Correspondence, 1966 May - 1968 December (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - General, 1966-1968 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1969 January - 1969 October (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - General, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1969 November-1971 December (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Secretary of the Senate, 1969-1980 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - Chair's Correspondence, 1969-1981 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Correspondence - General, 1971 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Correspondence Re: Coffee Hours, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Archives - General Correspondence, 1971-1980 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1972 January-1986 February (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 11)
  - Correspondence - General, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Correspondence - General, 1974 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Correspondence - General, 1975-1976 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Correspondence - General, 1977 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Correspondence - General, 1978 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Correspondence - General, 1978-1979 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Correspondence - General, 1979-1981 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Chair's Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Chair's Correspondence, 1984-1988 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, 1988-1994 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 21)
  - Chair's Correspondence, 1989 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 22)
  - Correspondence with the University Faculty Senate, 1989-1993 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 23)
  - Chair's Correspondence, 1990 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 24)
  - Chair's Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 25)
  - Chair's Correspondence, 1993-1996 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 26)
  - Chair's Correspondence, 1997-1999 (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 27)
  - Correspondence - General, Undated (Box 1 (8-Correspondence), Folder 28)
- Plenaries, 2008-2014; 11
- Policies, Methodology, and Instructions, 2012-2013; 12
- Subject Files, 1965-1999; 13; 1.67 cubic ft.
  Arranged chronologically
  Miscellaneous subject files maintained by the University Senate primarily relating to committees and task forces such as those on the environment, firearms, government, students ratings of faculty, as well as general correspondence files.
  - University Auxiliary Service, 1965-1976 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Clippings from Campus Courier, 1966-1969 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Parking, 1966-1974 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Physical Education, 1967-1972 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Salary Requests, 1967-1973 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Ph. D. Programs, 1967-1982 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Master's Programs, 1967-1983 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Certificate Programs, 1968-1979 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - B.A and B.S Programs, 1968-1981 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Faculty-Student Consultation, 1969-1971 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - The General College and Experimental College, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - S/U Grading, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Doctor of Arts Program, 1969-1972 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Academic Policy General Files, 1969-1977 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Clippings from Albany Student Press, 1969 September-1977 December (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - The CURE Proposal, 1970 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Clippings from the Tower Tribune, 1970-1973 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Affirmative Action - General Files, 1970-1976 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Graduate Academic Policy, 1970-1981 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Room Reservations, 1970-1989 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Middle States Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools - Accreditation, 1971 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Student Dwelling Incorporated, 1971 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - S/U Grading, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Emeritus Status, 1971-1973 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Communication Study, 1972 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Master Plan of the State University of New York - 1972. "Reaffirmation and Reform: Building a Comprehensive University for the 70's" (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Master Plan of the State University of New York, Summary Version - "Reaffirmation and Reform", 1972 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Pre-Registration (Lufti Proposal), 1972 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Firearms Policy (Folder 1), 1972-1973 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Withdrawal Policies, 1972-1978 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Faculty Senate Bulletin, 1973 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Prospectus for the University Center at Albany, 1973 March (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Prospectus for the University Center at Albany - Revised, 1973 June (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Fierarms Policy (Folder 2), 1973-1974 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - "Master Plan" or "Prospectus 1973-81" planning, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Clippings from Tower Tribune, 1973 October- 1977 December (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - S/U Grading, 1973-1984 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - United University Professions (UUP), 1974-1978 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Faculty Exchange Scholars Program, 1974-1981 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - American Association of University Professors (AAUP), 1975 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Prospectus for the University Center at Albany, 1975 July (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Five Quad Volunteer Ambulance Service, 1976 (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - The Regents Tentative Statewide Plan for the Development of Postsecondary Education, 1976 November (Box 1 (13-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Regents Tentative Statewide Plan for the Development of Postsecondary Education, Undated (Box 2 (13-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Regents Tentative Statewide Plan for the Development of Postsecondary Education, Comments, Undated (Box 2 (13-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Regents Tentative Statewide Plan for the Development of Postsecondary Education, Second Draft, Undated (Box 2 (13-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Affirmative Action - General Files, Undated (Box 2 (13-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - University Auxiliary Service, Undated (Box 2 (13-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Academic Policy General Files, Undated (Box 2 (13-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Programs and Priorities; Abstracts of Three-Year Plans- State University of New York at Albany, Undated (Box 2 (13-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Programs and Priorities of the State University of New York at Albany, Undated (Box 2 (13-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - University "FACT" Book, Undated (Box 2 (13-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Truth-in-Testing Bill, Undated (Box 2 (13-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Budget Panel, Undated (Box 2 (13-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Academic Policy General Files, 1979-1981 (Box 3 (13-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Middle States Association of Colleges and Schools Evaluation, 1980 (Box 3 (13-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - R.O.T.C, 1980-1982 (Box 3 (13-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Student Instructional Rating Form (SIRF), 1980-1984 (Box 3 (13-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - The Undergraduate Bulletin, 1983-1984 (Box 3 (13-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Office Equipment, 1985-1987 (Box 3 (13-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Budget Materials, 1986 (Box 3 (13-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Affirmative Action Plan, 1989 (Box 3 (13-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - "Toward a Prosperous Future" - Report of the Policy Steering Committee of the Governor's Conference on Science and Engineering Education, Research and Development, 1990 (Box 3 (13-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Faculty Senate Bulletin, 1990-1995 (Box 3 (13-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - University operations Committee - Publication "Award for Excellence in Equal Opportunity/Affirmative Action", 1991 April (Box 3 (13-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - University operations Committee - Publication "A Longitudinal Profile of the Faculty by Gender and Ethnicity", 1993 April (Box 3 (13-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - University operations Committee - Publication "Trends in Instruction - Class Sizes, Course Offerings, Methods of Instruction: An Analysis of CASA Data", 1996 April (Box 3 (13-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Distance Learning Committee of the University Faculty Senate Interim Report, 1995 January (Box 3 (13-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Faculty Senate Bulletin, 1995-1997 (Box 3 (13-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Faculty Senate Bulletin, 1997-1998 (Box 3 (13-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Conference on Instructional Technologies (CIT) - Seventh Annual, 1998 (Box 3 (13-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Faculty Senate Bulletin, 1998-1999 (Box 3 (13-Subject Files), Folder 18)
- Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies, 1962-1999; 14; 1.17 cubic ft.
  Records of Senate Committiees and Task Forces without permanent, standing status.
  - Collections Committee, 1962-1963 (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 1)
  - University Bookstore Advisory Board, 1966 (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 2)
  - Faculty Affairs Council, 1966-1969 (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 3)
  - Grievance and Complaint Committee, 1967-1972 (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 4)
  - Senate Colloquium for NYEA or UUP, 1967-1972; 1978 (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 5)
  - Personnel Policies Council Agendas and Minutes, 1968 January-1969 October (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 6)
  - Personnel Policies Council Faculty Handbook Committee, 1968 October- 1969 May (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 7)
  - Personnel Policies Council Reports to Senate, 1968 September-1969 December (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 8)
  - Personnel Policies Council Social and Charitable Activities Committee, 1968 December-1969 May (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 9)
  - Personnel Policies Council Treasurer's Reports, 1968 January-1969 May (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 10)
  - Personnel Policies Council Reports, 1968-1970 (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 11)
  - Personnel Policies Council Annual Reports, 1968-1969; 1971-1972 (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 12)
  - Personnel Policies Council Correspondence, 1968 June-1971 May (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 13)
  - Personnel policies council Committee on Academic Freedom and Professional Ethics and Grievance Procedures, 1968 October-1969 October; Undated (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 14)
  - Personnel Policies Council Parking Committee, 1969 (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 15)
  - Personnel Policies Council Faculty Economic and Professional Welfare Committee, 1969 October-1970 (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 16)
  - Faculty-Student Consultation Guidelines Ad Hoc Committee, 1969 May-1971 May (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 17)
  - Awards and opportunities for Advanced Study Committee, 1969-1973 (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 18)
  - Search Committee for President, 1969-1978 (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 19)
  - Environmental Decisions Commission, 1969-1979 (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 20)
  - Academic Regulations, Task Force on, 1970 (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 21)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Senatorial Authority, 1970 (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 22)
  - Faculty Evaluation and Term Renewal, Tenure and Promotion Criteria Ad Hoc Committee, 1970 December-1971 April (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 23)
  - Graduate Teaching Assistants, Report of the Committee on the Training of, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 24)
  - Personnel Policies Council Parking Committee, 1970 March-1971 December (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 25)
  - Personnel Policies Council Treasurer's Reports, 1970 November-1971 May (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 26)
  - Personnel Policies Council Bills and Resolutions, 1970-1972 (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 27)
  - Personnel Policies Council Reports to Senate, 1970 May; 1972 (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 28)
  - University Evaluation and Improvement Council, 1970 November-1972 May (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 29)
  - Outstanding Teaching Awards Committee, 1970-1975 (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 30)
  - Instruction, Task Force on, 1970; 1978 (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 31)
  - Judicial Workshop Steering Committee, 1971 (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 32)
  - Senate Professional Association (SPA), 1971 (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 33)
  - Personnel Policies Council Agendas and Minutes, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 34)
  - Personnel Policies Council Correspondence, 1971 September-1972 July (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 35)
  - Personnel Policies Council Grievance Committee, 1971 October-1972 (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 36)
  - Personnel Policies Council Faculty Handbook Committee, 1971 October-1972 January (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 37)
  - Personnel Policies Council SPA/PPC Joint Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 38)
  - Council on University Evaluation and Improvement, 1972 (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 39)
  - Grants for the Improvement of Undergraduate Instruction, Campus Committee for, 1972 (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 40)
  - Personnel Policies Council Group Insurance, 1972 (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 41)
  - University Scholars Ad Hoc Committee, 1972 (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 42)
  - Personnel Policies Council Parking Committee, 1972 January -1973 April (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 43)
  - Committee on Discretionary Salary Increases, 1972-1974 (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 44)
  - Committee on Student Evaluation of Teachers, 1972-1974 (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 45)
  - Academic Services Council, 1972 January-1976 May (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 46)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on By-Laws, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 47)
  - Academic Program Priorities, Select Committee on, 1974-1975 (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 48)
  - Academic Program Priorities, Report of Select Committee on, 1975 May 15 (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 49)
  - Ad-Hoc Committee of Cognate Disciplines on Promotion and Continuing Appointment, 1975 (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 50)
  - Concerned Faculty, the Committee of, 1976-1977 (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 51)
  - Search Committee for Vice President, 1976-1979 (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 52)
  - Search Committee for Assistant Vice President for Academic Affairs, 1977-1978; Undated (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 53)
  - Undergraduate Education, Special Committee on, 1979 (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 54)
  - Regulations of the Commissioner of Education, Ad Hoc Committee on the, 1979-1980 (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 55)
  - University Senate Study Committee, 1980 (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 56)
  - Distribution Requirements, Report of the Special Committee on, 1981 (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 57)
  - Archives of Public Affairs and Policy Ad-Hoc Faculty Advisory Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 58)
  - Student Ethics and Cheating, Task Force on, 1982-1983 (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 59)
  - Task Force on Library Construction, 1985; 1987-1990; Undated (Box 1 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 60)
  - Steering Committee for Planning For Review of Undergraduate Education, 1976; 1977; Undated (Box 2 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 1)
  - Committee on Faculty Names, 1987-1988 (Box 2 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 2)
  - Facilities Names, Committee on, 1987-1988 (Box 2 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 3)
  - Sexuality Week, Ad Hoc Committee to Review, 1989 (Box 2 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 4)
  - Sexuality Week, Ad Hoc Committee to Review; Review Materials-Pamphlets, 1989 (Box 2 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 5)
  - Committee on Academic Dishonesty, 1989-1990 (Box 2 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 6)
  - University Mission Task Force, 1991-1999 (Box 2 (14-Temporary and Ad Hoc Bodies), Folder 7)
- Councils and Committees, 1950-2011; 15; 16.69 cubic ft.
  - Executive Committee, 1966-2011; 15.1; 3.17 cubic ft.